you know, what's weird is AI
allows you,
it has a system you can build,
and you can build it this way.
This is something that'll
happen that'll go
in and look at all your
comments. And if there's any,
any good ideas
in those comments, then you
could say, well,
can you use this good idea? To
build me something similar or
build it
even better. And then, if you
already have a nice,
substantial idea, historical
record with these systems,
then, of course, what it builds
you is probably going to be
different than
what it builds me. What it
builds you is probably going to
be more
in alignment with your
capabilities and abilities of
what you do,
unless you've told it to
disregard all of that.
Next time somebody asks you the
question of,
so how are you doing this? What
are you using it for?
How exactly are you putting it
into play?
and they say, hey, comment
below, you can comment below,
but try not to give up your
game plan.